RG 002:025, Appropriations Committee
Connecticut State Library
Appropriations Committee records
1901-2000
Connecticut State Library
Connecticut. General Assembly. Committee on Appropriations
24.75 cubic feet
Appropriations Committee meeting files and block grant material.
RG002_025_APP
Multiple
Scope and Content
These records contain primarily meeting files and other material related to block grants.
Arrangement
Arranged by accession.
Index Terms
Organizations:
Connecticut. General Assembly. Committee on Appropriations
Subjects:
Administrative agencies -- Connecticut -- Finance; Connecticut -- Appropriations and expenditures; Connecticut. General Assembly. Committee on Appropriations -- Records and correspondence; Fiscal policy -- Connecticut; Legislative bodies -- Public meetings -- Connecticut
Document Types:
Agendas; Membership lists; Minutes; Reports; Testimonies; Transcripts
Restrictions on Access
These records are stored at an off-site facility and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
See the policy.
Container List
- Accession SL148942, 1901
  - Meeting minutes, Vol. 1, 1901; 1 volume (Box Shared box)
    See Accession 2002-084 for Volume 2.
- Accession SL060379, 1911
  - Meeting minutes, 1911; 1 volume (Box Shared box)
- Accession 1986-047A, 1985
  - Generally Accepted Accounting Principals, 1985 (Box 1-2)
- Accession 1986-047B, 1985
  - Bradley Fire Training Facilities, 1985 (Box 1)
- Accession 1986-047C, 1985
  - State Collective Bargaining, 1985 (Box 1)
- Accession 1994-005, 1989
  - Joint meeting of Appropriations Committee, Energy and Public Utilities Committee and Human Services Commission.
    - Connecticut Restitution Plan for Petroleum Settlement Funds, 1989; 1 envelope
- Accession 1998-043, 1982-1986, 1997
  - Legislative correspondence, 1982-1985 (Box 1)
  - Energy assistance block grant (plus amendments), 1983 (Box 1)
  - Title XX block social services block grant - surplus funds, 1983 (Box 1)
  - Community services block grant allocation plan 1982-1983 (Box 1)
  - Social services block grant letter of transmittal, 1983 August 18 (Box 1)
  - Energy assistance block grants, 1983 (Box 1)
  - Emergency jobs act, 1983 (Box 1)
  - Alcohol, drug abuse & mental health services block grant allocation plan, 1983 (Box 1)
  - Warner amendment - plan for spending interest funds, 1983 (Box 1)
  - Maternal and child health block grant, 1982-1983 (Box 1)
  - Testimonies on legislative bills, 1997; 7 folders (Box 1)
  - Road blocks - drunk driving, 1982-1986 (Box 2)
  - FFY 1984-1985 Low-income home energy assistance block grant (Box 2)
  - NIS social services block grant allocation fund, 1984 (Box 2)
  - Alcohol, drug abuse, mental health services block grant (tech. revisions), 1984 (Box 2)
  - Governor's education block grant advisory committee recommendations, 1984 (Box 2)
  - ADM block grant (format f/allocation plan), 1984 (Box 2)
  - 1983-1984 low income energy assistance block grant (Box 2)
  - Maternal and child health services block grant, 1984 (Box 2)
  - Preventive health and health services block grant and allocation plan, 1984 (Box 2)
  - Technical revision - FFY 1985 maternal and child health services block grant, 1984 (Box 2)
  - FFY 1984-1985 social services block grant (Box 2)
  - Community services block grant 1984-1985 allocation plan (Box 2)
  - Alcohol, drug abuse and mental health block grant FFY 1984-1985 (Box 2)
  - 1984 Alcohol, drug abuse & mental health services block grant allocation plan (Box 2)
  - 1981-1982, 1982-1983, 1983-1984 Amendment to low income home energy assistance block grant (Box 2)
  - Warner Fund (Petroleum violation escrow funds), 1984 (Box 2)
  - Amendment 1983-1984 low income home energy assistance block grant (Box 2)
  - State distribution plan for AMOCO refund, 1984 (Box 2)
  - Small cities community block grant, 1984 (Box 2)
  - 1982-1983 Maternal and child health services block grant / technical (Box 2)
  - Mother and child health and preventive health block grants, 1984 (Box 2)
  - Special weatherization demonstration program (OPM/Energy Division) Amend. to 1982-1983 low income energy assistance block grant, 1984 (Box 2)
  - Comments about block grant by Gary King of OPM, 1984 (Box 2)
  - Judicial Department contract, 1982-1983 (Box 2)
  - Preventive health and health services block grant FY 1984-1985 (Box 2)
  - Maternal and child health, preventive health & health services and alcohol, drug abuse and mental health block grants, 1983 (Box 2)
  - Social services block grant underruns, FY 1981-1982, 1983 (Box 2)
  - Community services block grant FY 1983-1984 allocation (Box 2)
  - Social services block grant jobs bill portion, 1983 (Box 2)
  - Social services block grant (Dept. of Human Services) report, 1983 (Box 2)
  - Testimonies on legislative bills, 1997 (Box 3-4)
    There is much duplication.
- Accession 1999-059, 1982-1994
  - Minutes and hearings, 1982 July 29 - 1984 April 9 (Box 1)
  - Minutes and hearings, 1984 April 11 - 1994 March 31 (Box 2)
- Accession 1999-097, 1983-1991
  - Report on the Commission on State Mandate to Cities and Towns, 1983 (Box 1)
  - Teachers' Retirement Board, 1985-1988 (Box 1)
  - Connecticut Restitution Plan for Petroleum Settlement Funds, 1986 (Box 1)
  - Connecticut Siting Council, 1986, 1988-1989 (Box 1)
  - Revised Estimates for State Aid to Municipalities, 1987 (Box 1)
  - State Technical College, 1987 (Box 1)
  - State Treasurer, undated (Box 1)
  - Statewide Emergency Telecommunications, Bureau of, 1988 (Box 1)
  - Status of Women, Commission on, undated (Box 1)
  - Student Loan Foundation, 1988-1989 (Box 1)
  - Department of Transportation, 1989-1990 (Box 1)
  - Secretary of the State, 1987-1989 (Box 1)
  - Southern Connecticut State University, 1989 (Box 1)
  - Special Revenue, Division of, 1983-1984, 1987 (Box 1)
  - State Insurance Purchasing Board, undated (Box 1)
  - Regional Community College, 1987 (Box 1)
  - DRS / Neighborhood Association Act, 1989 (Box 1)
  - Revenue Services, Dept. of, 1987-1989 (Box 1)
  - State Police Union, undated (Box 1)
  - Telecommunications Networks and Information Systems Cost, 1986 (Box 1)
  - CT Telecommunications Task Force (interim report), 1985 (Box 1)
  - Unions, 1986-1989 (Box 1)
  - Special Tax Obligation Bonds, 1990 June 30 (Box 1)
  - Special Transportation Fund (interim report), 1990 (Box 2)
  - Agendas, 1990 (Box 2)
  - Preliminary Fiscal Notes, 1990-1991 (Box 2)
- Accession 1999-105, 1975
  - Subcommittee on Leasing final report, 1975; 1 volume (Box Shared box)
- Accession 2001-026, 1993-2000
  - Public hearing testimony, 1995-2000
    - Governors' budget proposal, 1995 February 21 - March 1
      - General testimony from public (ex. CBIA), 1995 February 21 (Box 1)
      - General government A, 1995 February 21 (Box 1)
      - General government B, 1995 February 21 (Box 1)
      - Conservation and development, 1995 February 22 (Box 1)
      - Higher education, 1995 February 23 (Box 1)
      - Transportation, 1995 February 23 (Box 1)
      - Elementary and secondary education, 1995 February 24 (Box 1)
      - Judicial and corrections, 1995 February 24 (Box 1)
      - Legislative, 1995 February 24 (Box 1)
      - Health and hospitals, 1995 February 27 (Box 1)
      - Regulation and protection, 1995 February 28 (Box 1)
      - Human services, 1995 March 1 (Box 1)
    - State central warehouse, 1995 September 29; 2 accordion folders (Box 1)
    - Waiver applications from DSS for (1) personal assistance services and (2) acquired brain injury home and community based services, 1996 January 12 (Box 2)
    - Deficiency budget briefing, 1996 February 8 (Box 2)
    - Governor's proposed budget, 1996 February 13, 15; 5 accordion folders (Box 2)
    - Governor's proposed budget, 1996 February 15, 22, March 13, 19; 5 accordion folders (Box 3)
    - Proposed substitute for SB579, 1996 April 10 (Box 3)
    - Governor's proposed budget, 1997 February 14-27; 2 accordion folders (Box 3)
    - Governor's proposed budget, 1998 February 10, 13; 2 accordion folders (Box 4)
    - Various bills, 1998 March 11 (Box 4)
      The bulk concerns changes to the Teachers' Retirement System.
    - Information forum on campus-based financial aid, 1998 March 13 (Box 4)
    - Compensation of elected officials, 1998 March 19 (Box 4)
    - Deficiency bill 5022, 1998 March 19 (Box 4)
    - Governor's proposed budget, 1999 February 17 - (Box 4)
      - Higher education, 1999 February 17 (Box 4)
      - General government B and A, 1999 February 18 (Box 4)
      - Conservation and development, 1999 February 19 (Box 4)
      - Transportation, 1999 February 19 (Box 4)
      - Transportation and conservation and development, 1999 February 19 (Box 5)
      - Health and hospitals, 1999 February 22, 23; 4 accordion folders (Box 5)
      - Elementary and secondary education, 1999 February 23 (Box 5)
      - Judicial and corrections, 1999 February 23 (Box 5)
      - Regulation and protection, 1999 February 24; 2 accordion folders (Box 5)
      - Master set budget testimony (Box 5)
      - Human services, 1999 February 25 - March 5; 4 accordion folders + single folders (Box 6)
      - Municipal forum, 1999 March 17 (Box 6)
    - OPM testimony on various bills, 1999 March 31; 2 accordion folders (Box 6)
    - Tobacco settlement; Veterans; Teachers' retirement, 1999 March 31 (Box 6)
    - Deficiency bill HB 6759, 1999 April 13 (Box 6)
    - Dept. of Social Services, Office of the Commissioner, Joint hearing, 1999 April 21 (Box 6)
    - Dept. of Social Services block grant, 1999 May 25; 2 accordion folders (Box 6)
    - Projected state agency deficiencies, 1999 November 9 (Box 6)
    - Governor's proposed budget agency presentations, 2000 February 16, 18 (Box 7)
    - Governor's budget adjustments, 2000 February 23 (Box 7)
    - Proposed amendment to the Connecticut Energy Assistance Program, 2000 March 13 (Box 7)
    - Raised bills and Governor's bills, 2000 March 14 (Box 7)
    - Informational forum, 2000 March 16 (Box 7)
    - Adriaen's Landing, Joint Hearing Appropriations and Finance, 2000 March 30 (Box 7)
    - Public hearing, 2000 April 5 (Box 7)
  - Public hearing transcripts, 1995-2000
    - 1995 January 13 - February 22 (Box 7)
    - 1995 February 23 - November 9 (Box 8)
    - 1996 January 12 - 1997 February 25 (Box 9)
    - 1997 February 26 - 1998 March 25 (Box 10)
    - 1998 April 14 - 1999 February 22 (Box 11)
    - 1999 February 23 - September 15 (Box 12)
    - 1999 November 4 - 2000 November 30 (Box 13)
  - Reorganization studies material: agency organization charts, 1991-1993 (Box 14)
- Accession 2002-084, 1901
  - Meeting minutes, Vol. 2, 1901; 1 volume
    See Accession SL148942 for Volume 1.
- Accession 2008-010, 1996-1998
  - Public hearing on proposed settlement of Connecticut Hospital Association, et. al. v. Rowland, et. al., 1996 January 17 (Box 1)
  - Housing & Community Development Plan, 1996 April (Box 1)
  - Public hearing and committee meeting on drug control and system improvement formula grant program allocation plan, 1996 August 6 (Box 1)
  - Public hearing and committee meeting on petroleum settlement funds allocation plan, 1996 September 3 (Box 1)
  - Public hearing and committee meeting on community mental health services block grant allocation plan, 1996 October 4 (Box 1)
  - Public hearing and committee meeting on substance abuse prevention and treatment block grant allocation plan, 1996 October 4 (Box 1)
  - Public hearing and committee meeting on social services block grant allocation plan, 1996 October 4 (Box 1)
  - Public hearing and committee meeting on maternal and child health services block grant allocation plan, 1996 October 4 (Box 1)
  - Public hearing and committee meeting on preventive health services block grant allocation plan, 1996 October 4 (Box 1)
  - Public hearing and committee meeting on community service block grant allocation plan, 1996 October 8 (Box 1)
  - Public hearing and committee meeting on child care and development block grant allocation plan, 1996 October8 (Box 1)
  - Public hearing and committee meeting on amendments to the 1995-1996 CEAP/SAFA plan and the proposed 1996-1997 CEAP / SAFA plan, 1996 October 8 (Box 1)
  - Public hearing and committee meeting on local law enforcement block grants allocation plan, 1996 October 22 (Box 1)
  - Local law enforcement block grant, 1997 (Box 1)
  - 1997-1998 Allocation plan for drug control and system improvement formula block grant program, 1997 March 12 (Box 1)
  - Municipal informational forum, 1997 March 19 (Box 1)
  - Petroleum restitutionary plan, 1997 July 1 (Box 1)
  - Consolidated plan for housing and community development, 1997 Action plan, 1997 September 12 (Box 1)
  - 1997 Block grant day, 1997 September 26 (Box 1)
    For the following block grants: Substance abuse prevention and treatment, preventive health, maternal and child health, community mental health.
  - Welfare to work federal grants, 1998 January 28 (Box 2)
  - ECS public forum, Elementary and Secondary Education Subcommittee, 1998 February 27 (Box 2)
  - Municipal forum, 1998 March 5 (Box 2)
  - Medicaid waiver amendment, 1998 July 15 (Box 2)
  - Joint public hearing: Appropriations, Public Health, Human Services Committees, 1998 September 22 (Box 2)
    For the following block grants: substance abuse prevention and treatment, community mental health services, maternal and child health services, prventive health and health services, social services block grant, community services block grant.
  - Connecticut Energy Assistance Plan / State Appropriated Fuel Assistance (CEAP / SAFA), 1998 October 19 (Box 2)
- Accession 2013-009, 1899-1903
  - Ledger, 1899-1901 (Box 1)
    Columns for appropriations asked for and granted.
  - Ledger, 1903 (Box 1)
  - Meeting minutes, 1903 January 14 - June 2 (Box 1)